there we are folks
tamo smo ljudi
the newer newer how you gotta say it
noviji noviji kako to moraš da kažeš
right newer end w88 - so this is only 16
desno noviji w88 - to je samo 16
dollars on Amazon my friends let's get
dolara na Amazonu moji prijatelji
into the box and see what it comes with
u kutiju i da vidimo šta dolazi sa
so when I was on Amazon looking for a
pa kad sam bio na Amazonu tražeći
cheap microphone this came in as pretty
jeftin mikrofon je postao lijep
much the cheapest one that you can
najjeftiniji koji možete
possibly get she's ooh sixteen dollars
možda je dobila šesnaest dolara
for this and now it's a condenser
za ovo i sada je kondenzator
microphone so it does require phantom
mikrofon tako da zahtijeva fantom
power and you'll see some reviews on
moć i vidjet ćete neke o
Amazon that will say oh it has so much
Amazon koji će reći oh ima toliko toga
noise and all that those people don't
buka i sve što ti ljudi ne rade
know what phantom power is a guarantee
znam šta je fantomska snaga garancija
you have to power this microphone so you
Morate napajati ovaj mikrofon tako da vi
have to have a special kind of mixing
moraju imati posebnu vrstu miješanja
console that has power for this
konzola koja ima moć za to
microphone so if you plug it directly
mikrofon pa ako ga priključite direktno
into a computer it's gonna it's not
u kompjuter to neće
going to work you're gonna have to crank
ideš na posao , morat ćeš da pukneš
it up which is going to generate a whole
to koji će generirati cijeli
lot of noise because it doesn't your
Puno buke jer to nije tvoja
computer doesn't provide power to the
kompjuter ne daje snagu
microphone this is where I think that
mikrofon tu mislim da
confusion starts because they have
zbunjenost počinje jer imaju
provided an XLR to 8-inch microphone
obezbedio je XLR do 8-inčni mikrofon
adapter this looks like it would be
adapter izgleda ovako
compatible with a laptop computer so you
kompatibilan sa laptop računarom tako da i vi
plug it into your laptop computer you
uključite ga u svoj laptop računar
plug this into the microphone and you
uključite ga u mikrofon i vas
start testing it and it sounds like
počnite sa testiranjem i zvuči kao
garbage well your laptop computer does
đubre za smeće vaš laptop računar radi
not provide phantom power something like
ne pružaju fantomsku moć nešto slično
a zoom h4n it would provide phantom
zum h4n bi omogućio fantom
power over this cable however this is
međutim, ovaj kabl ima snagu
pretty much useless to the average user
prilično beskoristan za prosječnog korisnika
because you may not have that device so
jer možda nemate taj uređaj
you have to have you have to have a
morate imati morate imati
preamp for this that has phantom power
predpojačalo za ovo koje ima fantomsku moć
so watch for that
pa pazi na to
you're gonna need if you don't already
trebace ti ako već ne
have it you're gonna need something to
Imam to da ćeš trebati nešto da
work between this and the computer so
radi između ovog i računara
you can get fairly cheap like $49
možete dobiti prilično jeftini kao $ 49
preamps so you're gonna need one of
preamps, tako da ti treba jedna
those anyways here at the studio of
oni ionako ovdje u studiju
course we've got preamps here so it
Naravno, ovde imamo preampove
looks really nice it feels like it's a
Izgleda stvarno lepo izgleda kao da je
metal microphone and w88 too from new
metalni mikrofon i w88 također iz novog
air newer
air newer
it looks like it has a mic on the back
izgleda da ima mikrofon na poleđini
but it actually doesn't but it has the
ali to zapravo nije, ali ima
pop screen right built into the
pop ekran desno ugrađen u
microphone see that
mikrofon to vidi
so that's further your papa so that they
tako da je dalje tvoj tata tako da oni
don't pop the microphone make a big pop
nemojte iskljucivati ​​mikrofon
noise for $16 remember this kit okay we
buka za $ 16 zapamti ovaj kit u redu mi
get everything that you see here comes
dobiti sve što vidite ovdje dolazi
with an it's a sealed bag comes with a
sa zapečaćenom torbom dolazi sa
shock mount now I use a rode nt1
shock mount sada koristim rode nt1
microphone this would be perfectly
mikrofon bi to bilo savršeno
compatible with that so you can use this
kompatibilan s tim, tako da možete koristiti ovo
with any studio microphone you just pop
sa bilo kojim studio mikrofon samo pop
your microphone in here and what that
mikrofon ovde i šta to
does is it absorbs some of the vibration
on apsorbuje neke vibracije
that's going to be on the floor from you
to će biti na podu od tebe
moving your feet things like that as
pomerate noge tako
this sits on the stand so that piece in
ovo stoji na štandu tako da je taj komad unutra
and of itself is worth more than I paid
i sama po sebi vrijedi više nego što sam platio
for this kit which is pretty impressive
za ovaj kit koji je prilično impresivan
so even if I just wanted it for that and
pa čak i ako sam to želeo za to i
then I've got the extra extra microphone
onda imam dodatni ekstra mikrofon
to use because who knows how this is
koristiti jer ko zna kako je to
going to function right specifications
funkcionisanje ispravnih specifikacija
wise I mean they do boast that it's 20
mislim da se hvale da je 20
to 20,000 Hertz
do 20.000 Hertza
it's a unidirectional cardioid pickup
to je jednosmerni kardioidni podizač
pattern so what that means if we look at
šablon tako da to znači ako pogledamo
the head of the microphone so I'm gonna
glava mikrofona, tako da ću
be talking singing voicing into this
govoriti peva izražavajući u ovom
part here with the pop screen and so the
deo ovde sa pop ekranom i tako dalje
polar pattern is going to be in this
polar pattern će biti u ovom
shape so it's right in front of it
oblikovati tako da je ispred nje
anything behind it it's not going to
ništa iza toga neće
pick it up because the polar pattern is
pokupite ga jer je polarni uzorak
going forward it's unidirectional
napredovanje je jednosmerno
cardioid polar pattern so that's gonna
kardioidni polarni uzorak tako da će to biti
work really really well even I think in
radite stvarno jako dobro čak i kada mislim
our studio here where we've got some fan
naš studio ovde gde imamo fan
noise and things like that we'll be able
buku i slične stvari ćemo moći
to cut that out fairly easily certainly
smanjiti da se prilično lako sigurno
in a home studio environment that works
u okruženju kućnog studija koje radi
really well I'm gonna move back to the
Vrlo dobro. Idem nazad u
studio set here bring a couple of pieces
studio postavi ovdje nekoliko komada
with me I think the most challenging
sa mnom mislim da je najizazovniji
aspect of that microphone is the name
aspekt tog mikrofona je ime
this is the type of microphone that I
ovo je tip mikrofona koji ja
brought I'm just gonna call it the NW
doveo sam samo da ga nazovem SZ
eight 8/2 it's a really yeah it's a
osam 8/2 stvarno je da
funny funny name for sure it's a brand
smešno smešno ime sigurno je brend
that is available on Amazon and they
koji je dostupan na Amazonu i oni
have a fair number of pretty good little
Imamo dosta dobrih stvari
devices it's pretty miscellaneous it's
Uređaji su prilično raznovrsni
located made in China stuff but they
nalazi se u Kini, ali oni
have pretty good products
imaju prilično dobre proizvode
so that's okay no I'm just thinking the
tako da je u redu ne samo razmišljam o
curiosity is could it possibly be good
Radoznalost je da li bi to moglo biti dobro
enough to use this is the question this
dovoljno da biste koristili ovu je ovo pitanje
is the question the question so we can
pitanje je pitanje tako da možemo
tighten that up you see that now the
zategnite da vidite da je sada
shock mount moves around yeah so I can
šok se kreće oko ja, tako da mogu
adjust that perfectly based on where my
prilagodite to savršeno na osnovu mog položaja
stand is position and then that's just
stajalište je pozicija i onda je to samo
gonna pop right in there pop screen is
Pop će se pojaviti tamo
that what it's called up here yeah on
da je ono što se zove ovde da na
the microphone itself so as I'm laying
sam mikrofon tako da ja ležim
down from fat Rimes it's not gonna take
Od debelog Rimesa to neće uzeti
the cording videos right it's just a
video zapisi su samo a
little bit in like the more expensive
Malo kao u skuplje
ones the ones that are like mm like box
one su slične kutiji mm
em right yeah big flat thing yeah and
em pravo yeah veliki stan stvar da i
you can buy them so that it clips onto
možete ih kupiti tako da se na njih stavi klip
the stand and it sits in front of the
štand i on sedi ispred
microphone but that's another $20 to add
mikrofon, ali to je još 20 dolara
to the kit this one's got it built-in
na komplet ova je dobila ugrađeni
and there's sixteen dollars for
i za 16 dolara
everything now it doesn't include the
sve sada ne uključuje
stand obviously this stand is my own so
očigledno je da je ovaj stav moj
you will need a stand you can put it on
trebat će vam štand možete staviti ga na
a desktop stand if you want as long as
desktop stand, ako želite sve dok
it's got the ability to screw into a mic
ima mogućnost da zašara mikrofon
stand I did notice that in the Box there
Ja sam to primetio u kutiji
I don't know if you saw it we can
Ne znam da li ste to videli
probably see no we can't there's a
verovatno ne vidimo da ne možemo
little black piece in the box that will
mali crni komad u kutiji koji će
adapt this to the two different sizes of
prilagoditi ovaj na dvije različite veličine
mic stand so it came with that adapter
mikrofonom tako da je došao s tim adapterom
as well should we give it a try I'm
kao i da pokušamo da budem
going to just kind of put this right
samo ću ovo ispraviti
here
ovdje
and I need to get a cable and we'll need
i moram da nabavim kabl i trebaće nam
to turn off your headset microphone
da biste isključili mikrofon sa slušalica
because everything that you're gonna
jer sve što ćeš
hear is going to be from this microphone
čuje se iz ovog mikrofona
alright good good okay all right I'm
dobro dobro dobro dobro dobro sam
gonna I'm gonna disconnect all of our
Hoću da isključim sve naše
microphones so you're not gonna hear our
mikrofoni tako da nećete čuti naše
headsets anymore everything's going to
više slušalice sve će ići
come from this as soon as I plug in that
dolazim iz ovoga čim se priključim
cable yeah all right okay sure and I can
kabla da, dobro je, dobro i mogu
disconnect mine because we're gonna plug
Isključi moj, jer ćemo ga uključiti
into my mic cable here
u moj mikrofonski kabel
[Music]
[Music] \ t
testing testing 2 4 6 Mic Check 1 2 3 5
testiranje testiranja 2 4 6 Mic Check 1 2 3 5
4 3 when you put them all together then
4 3 kada ih sve zajedno sastavite
you got a lot of game you don't have to
imaš mnogo igre koju ne moraš
worry about the quality of sound it's
brinite o kvalitetu zvuka
gonna be great if it's coming from the
će biti super ako dolazi iz
ground I'm gonna start small but we're
Zemlju ću početi malo, ali smo
gonna stand tall we're gonna say it
stajat će visoko i reći ćemo
right
pravo
turn with the mic we're gonna start
okreni se sa mikrofonom koji ćemo početi
small but we're gonna stand tall was
mali ali ćemo stajati visok
gonna say you're right gotta start with
Reći ću da si u pravu
the mic what Suzanne my ex and soundless
mikrofon kakav je Suzanne moj bivši i bez zvuka
you like that sound that you'd like
volite taj zvuk koji želite
gotta start with that bike voices and
moram početi sa tim glasovima bicikla i
mites and things that you like got a
grinje i stvari koje volite
sound that you like got a start without
zvuk koji vam se sviđa bez njega
Mike you don't got a mic then you got no
Majk koji nemaš mikrofon, onda nemaš
sound and if you ain't got no sound and
zvuk i ako nemate zvuk i
you can't be found well if you don't
ne možete se naći dobro ako to ne učinite
like this Mike a sixteen dollar by won't
kao što je ovaj Majk šesnaest dolara po volji
be too hard on your wallet so hey give
budi previše tvrd na novčaniku, tako da ti ga daš
it a try more importance that your Mike
pokušaj više važnosti da tvoj Mike
is that as a rapper you're alright that
da je kao reper u redu to
your lyrics are important and what you
Vaši tekstovi su važni i ono što vi
mean is out of sight gotta say what you
znači da je iz vidokruga morao reći šta ti
want gotta say what you like and to do
hoću da kažem šta ti se sviđa i da radiš
those things you need a dang good but
te stvari koje ti trebaju dang dobro ali
we've gotta start small but we're gonna
Moramo početi mali, ali ćemo
stand tall gotta say right
stojim u vis, moram da kažem kako treba
we gotta start small but we're gonna
Moramo početi mali ali ćemo
stand tall got a singer right voices and
Stani malo dobio pjevač pravo glasa i
might extend things that you like that
može proširiti stvari koje vam se sviđaju
telling you lies gotta start with that
reći da laži moraju početi s tim
mic voices the head Mike said that yes
Mikro glasovi glave Majk je rekao da
you like that sound that you like you
volite taj zvuk koji vam se dopada
gotta start with that light Oh was that
moram početi s tim svjetlom Oh je to bilo
worth $16 please send your comments
vredan 16 dolara, pošaljite vaše komentare
through yeah comment below I think God's
kroz yeah komentar ispod Mislim da je Bog
great starting point for sure yeah what
odlična polazna tačka sigurno da šta
a world we live in
svijet u kojem živimo
yeah very cool you can get yours at cat5
yeah very cool možete dobiti svoj na cat5
dot TV slash mic check it out it's only
dot TV slash mikrofon provjerite samo
sixteen bucks or so so let us know what
šesnaest dolara ili tako da nam javite šta
you think
ti misliš
[Music]
[Music] \ t
[Applause]
[Aplauz]